Jacqueline Moore

Biomedical Engineering & English at UC Davis

jackymoore.com (650) 759-8154 jacmoore@ucdavis.edu

Relevant Skills

Web Design / Created websites using Squarespace for two companies (BioInnovation Group and The Arthur Morgan Institute for Community Solutions). Coded personal website (jackymoore.com) from scratch.

Writing (content, technical, journalistic) / Four years of experience in writing for tech companies, nonprofits, and newspapers. Able to write in different styles for different mediums.

Content Creation / Strong background in designing customer-facing visuals and graphics. Adept photographer; see personal website (jackymoore.com) for portfolio.

Education

University of California, Davis / Biomedical Engineering (B.S.) & English (B.A.)

SEPTEMBER 2017 - DECEMBER 2021 (expected graduation date), DAVIS (CA)

Microfluidics Team Lead at **BioInnovation Group**. Copy Editor at **The California Aggie**. Member of the **Society of Women Engineers**. Member of the **Pre-Law Association**.

Experience

Salesforce / Technical Writing Intern (Einstein Analytics)

JUNE 2019 - PRESENT, SAN FRANCISCO (CA)

Salesforce is a software company that engineers customer relationship management services.

Composing user interface text for Einstein Analytics, Salesforce's data analysis software. Also using Einstein Analytics to create interactive customer support resources.

BioInnovation Group / Chief Content Officer

JANUARY 2018 - PRESENT, DAVIS (CA)

BioInnovation Group is a biotech incubator for undergraduate students at UC Davis.

Created new design, pages, and content for the company website. Revamping the onboarding process for new researchers.

The California Aggie / Copy Editor

MARCH 2018 - PRESENT, DAVIS (CA)

The California Aggie is UC Davis' student-run newspaper.

Editing 20-30 articles per week using The Aggie's style guide. Previously a reporter for the campus news desk.

remote.it / Technical Writing Intern

JUNE 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018, PALO ALTO (CA)

remote.it (pronounced "remote-it") is a network security start-up.

Wrote user help guides about implementing new software features, such as bulk scripting. Helped launch customer-facing email campaign for publicizing product updates.

The Stanford Daily / Intern Reporter

JUNE 2016 - AUGUST 2016, STANFORD (CA)

The Stanford Daily is Stanford University's student-run newspaper.

Wrote articles about campus news, events, and faculty. Photographed campus events and edited images with Adobe Lightroom.

Palo Alto Housing / Marketing Intern

JUNE 2016 - AUGUST 2016, PALO ALTO (CA)

Palo Alto Housing is a nonprofit that manages affordable housing communities in Palo Alto and neighboring communities. Launched client interview protocol for company outreach project. Composed news briefs about company's property acquisitions. Designed fliers for company events in local communities.

The Arthur Morgan Institute for Community Solutions / Research Intern

JUNE 2015 - JUNE 2015, YELLOW SPRINGS (OH)

Community Solutions is an environmental nonprofit that promotes education about sustainable living practices.

Conducted research into the Keystone XL Pipeline to assist other interns in writing a grant about tar sands oil pipelines near the Canada-United States border. Also helped revamp the company's website, community solution.org. (The site has since been updated.)